<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.filestash.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <extends>org.kde.dolphin.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.konqueror.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.krusader.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.gwenview.desktop</extends>
  <name>FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">التخزين المؤقت</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Faililadu</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">फ़ाइल-स्टेश</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">PrzechowalniaPlików</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Filestash</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxFileStashxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">FileStash</name>
  <summary>A lightweight solution for virtual folder support in KDE Applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">حل خفيف الوزن لدعم المجلد الافتراضي للتخزين المؤقت في تطبيقات كدي</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Una solució lleugera per a permetre carpetes virtuals a les aplicacions KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Una solució lleugera per a permetre carpetes virtuals en les aplicacions KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Eine leichtgewichtige Lösung für die Unterstützung von virtuellen Ordner in KDE-Anwendungen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Μια ελαφριά λύση υποστήριξης εικονικών φακέλων στις KDE Εφαρμογές</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">A lightweight solution for virtual folder support in KDE Applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Una solución liviana para implementar carpetas virtuales en las aplicaciones de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Lihtne lahendus virtuaalsete kataloogide toetuse pakkumiseks KDE rakendustes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">KDEren aplikazioetan alegiazko karpetak erabili ahal izateko irtenbide arin bat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Kevyt KDE Applicationsin virtuaalikansiotuen ratkaisu.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Une solution légère de prise en charge des dossiers virtuels dans les applications KDE.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Unha solución sinxela para fornecer compatibilidade con cartafoles virtuais en aplicacións de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">एक हलका साधन जो केडीई अनुप्रयोगों के लिए वर्चुअल फ़ोल्डर का समर्थन देता है।</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Sebuah solusi yang ringan untuk dukungan folder virtual dalam Aplikasi KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Una soluzione leggera per il supporto delle cartelle virtuali nelle applicazioni KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">ვირტუალური საქაღალდეების მხარდაჭერა KDE-ის აპლიკაციებში</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">KDE 프로그램의 가벼운 가상 폴더 지원</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een lichtgewicht oplossing voor ondersteuning van virtuele mappen in KDE Applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Enkel løysing for støtte av virtuelle mapper i program frå KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Lekkie rozwiązanie obsługi wirtualnych katalogów w Aplikacjach KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Uma solução leve para o suporte de pastas virtuais nas Aplicações do KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Uma solução leve para suporte a pastas virtuais no KDE Applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Soluție simplă pentru susținerea dosarelor virtuale în aplicații KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Jednoduché riešenie pre podporu virtuálnych priečinkov v KDE aplikáciách.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Lahka rešitev za podporo virtualne mape v aplikacijah KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">En lättviktig lösning för stöd av virtuella kataloger i KDE-program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">KDE Uygulamalarında, sanal klasör desteği için hafif bir çözüm</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Невибагливий до ресурсів інструмент підтримки віртуальних тек у програмах KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxA lightweight solution for virtual folder support in KDE Applicationsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">为 KDE 应用提供虚拟文件夹支持的轻量化解决方案。</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Selecting multiple files in any file manager for copying and pasting has never been a pleasant experience, especially if the files are in a non-continuous order. Often, when selecting files using Ctrl+A or the selection tool, we find that we need to select only a subset of the required files we have selected. This leads to the unwieldy operation of removing files from our selection. Of course, the common workaround is to create a new folder and to put all the items in this folder prior to copying, but this is a very inefficient and very slow process if large files need to be copied. Moreover Ctrl+Click requires fine motor skills to not lose the entire selection of files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">لم يكن تحديد ملفات متعددة في أي مدير ملفات للنسخ واللصق تجربة ممتعة أبدًا ، خاصةً إذا كانت الملفات بترتيب غير مستمر. في كثير من الأحيان ، عند تحديد الملفات باستخدام Ctrl + A أو أداة التحديد ، نجد أننا بحاجة إلى تحديد مجموعة فرعية فقط من الملفات المطلوبة التي حددناها. هذا يؤدي إلى عملية مزعجة لإزالة الملفات من اختيارنا. بالطبع ، الحل الشائع هو إنشاء مجلد جديد ووضع جميع العناصر في هذا المجلد قبل النسخ ، ولكن هذه عملية غير فعالة وبطيئة للغاية إذا كانت هناك حاجة لنسخ الملفات الكبيرة. علاوة على ذلك ، يتطلب Ctrl + Click مهارات حركية دقيقة حتى لا تفقد المجموعة الكاملة من الملفات.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">La selecció de múltiples fitxers en qualsevol gestor de fitxers per a copiar i enganxar mai ha estat una experiència agradable, especialment si els fitxers estan en un ordre no contigu. Sovint, en seleccionar fitxers usant Ctrl+A o l'eina de selecció, ens trobem que cal seleccionar només un subconjunt dels fitxers requerits que hem seleccionat. Això porta a la pesada tasca d'eliminar fitxers de la selecció. Per descomptat, l'alternativa més freqüent és crear una carpeta nova i posar tots els elements en aquesta carpeta abans de copiar-hi, però això és un procés molt ineficient i molt lent si cal copiar fitxers grans. A més, Ctrl+Clic requereix habilitats motores fines per a no perdre tota la selecció de fitxers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">La selecció de múltiples fitxers en qualsevol gestor de fitxers per a copiar i apegar mai ha sigut una experiència agradable, especialment si els fitxers estan en un ordre no contigu. Sovint, en seleccionar fitxers utilitzant Ctrl+A o l'eina de selecció, ens trobem que cal seleccionar només un subconjunt dels fitxers requerits que hem seleccionat. Açò porta a la pesada tasca d'eliminar fitxers de la selecció. Per descomptat, l'alternativa més freqüent és crear una carpeta nova i posar tots els elements en esta carpeta abans de copiar-hi, però açò és un procés molt ineficient i molt lent si cal copiar fitxers grans. A més, Ctrl+Clic requerix habilitats motores fines per a no perdre tota la selecció de fitxers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">At vælge flere filer i enhver filhåndtering til kopiering og indsættelse har aldrig været en behagelig oplevelse, specielt hvis filerne ikke er i fortløbende rækkefølge. Oftest når du vælger filer med Ctrl+A eller markeringsværktøjet, så finder du ud af at du kun har brug for en del af de valgte filer. Det fører til den besværlige handlinger det er at fjerne filer fra markeringen. Man kan selvfølgelig bruge den almindelige løsning med at oprette en ny mappe og ligge alle elementerne i mappen inden kopiering, men det er en meget ineffektiv og meget langsom proces hvis der er store filer som skal kopieres. Desuden kræver Ctrl+klik de nødvendige finmotoriske evner for ikke at miste hele filmarkeringen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Η επιλονή πολλών αρχείων σε οποιονδήποτε διαχειριστή αρχείων για αντιγραφή και επικόλληση δεν είναι ποτέ μια ευχάριστη εμπειρία, ειδικά αν τα αρχεία δεν είναι συνεχόμενα. Συχνά, όταν επιλέγουμε αρχεία με το Ctrl+A ή με το εργαλείο επιλογής, παρατηρούμε ότι χρειαζόμαστε μόνο ένα υποσύνολο από τα αρχεία που έχουμε επιλέξει. Αυτό οδηγεί στην άβολη διαδικασία να διαγράψουμε αρχεία από τα επιλεγμένα. Βέβαια η συνήθης λύση είναι να δημιουργήσουμε έναν νέο φάκελο και να βάλουμε όλα τα αντικείμενα εκεί πριν τα αντιγράψουμε, αλλά αυτή είναι μια πολύ αναποτελεσματική και αργή διεργασία αν απαιτείται η αντιγραφή μεγάλων αρχείων. Επιπλέον το Ctrl+Click απαιτεί λεπτές κινητικές δεξιότητες ώστε να μην αναιρεθεί όλη η επιλογή των αρχείων.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Selecting multiple files in any file manager for copying and pasting has never been a pleasant experience, especially if the files are in a non-continuous order. Often, when selecting files using Ctrl+A or the selection tool, we find that we need to select only a subset of the required files we have selected. This leads to the unwieldy operation of removing files from our selection. Of course, the common workaround is to create a new folder and to put all the items in this folder prior to copying, but this is a very inefficient and very slow process if large files need to be copied. Moreover Ctrl+Click requires fine motor skills to not lose the entire selection of files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">La selección de múltiples archivos en cualquier gestor de archivos para copiarlos y pegarlos nunca ha sido una experiencia agradable, especialmente si los archivos no son consecutivos. A menudo, cuando se seleccionan archivos usando Ctrl+A o la herramienta de selección, nos damos cuenta de que solo necesitamos seleccionar un subconjunto de los archivos que ya hemos seleccionado. Esto conduce a la poco manejable operación de eliminar archivos de la selección. Por supuesto, la solución común consiste en crear una nueva carpeta y colocar en ella todos los elementos antes de copiarlos, aunque esto es un proceso muy lento y poco eficiente si es necesario copiar archivos grandes. Además, Ctrl+clic necesita de habilidades motoras precisas para no perder toda la selección de archivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Paljude failide valimine kopeerimiseks ja asetamiseks ei ole kunagi üheski failihalduris olnud meeldiv tegevus, eriti veel kui failid ei asetse üksteise järel. Faile Ctrl + A või valikutööriista abil valides võib sageli leida, et tegelikult läheb meil valitute asemel tarvis ainult teatavat osa neist. See toob kaasa kohmaka valikust ebavajalike failide eemaldamise operatsiooni. Üks levinumaid lahendusi on mõistagi uue kataloogi loomine ja kõigi vajalike elementide paigutamine sinna enne kopeerimise alustamist, kuid see on üpris vähese tõhususega ja eriti juhul, kui failid on suured, ka päris aeglane protsess. Pealegi nõuab Ctrl + klõps väga head kontrolli liigutuste üle, et mitte kogemata tervet valikut kaotada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Kopiatu eta itsasteko fitxategi anitz hautatzea, berdin da zein fitxategi kudeatzaile erabili, ez da sekula zeregin atsegina izan, bereziki fitxategiak ez badaude elkarren jarraian. Maiz, Ktrl+A edo hautapen tresna erabiliz fitxategiak hautatzean, konturatzen gara aukeratu dugun fitxategien azpimultzo bat besterik ez dugula behar. Honek gure hautapeneko fitxategiak desautatzeko eragiketa astuna egitera garamatza. Noski, ohiko konponbidea karpeta berri bat sortu eta kopiatu aurretik fitxategi guztiak karpeta honetan ipintzea da, baina prozesu hau ez da oso eraginkorra eta oso motela da fitxategi handiak kopiatu behar direnean. Bestalde, fitxategien hautapen osoa ez galtzeko, Ktrl+Klik erabiltzean motrizitate ona behar da.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Useamman tiedoston valitseminen kopioitavaksi tai liitettäväksi ei milloinkaan missään tiedostonhallintaohjelmassa ole ollut helppoa, etenkään jos tiedostot eivät ole peräkkäin. Usein valittuaan tiedostoja Ctrl+A:lla tai valintatyökalulla huomaa, että tarvitseekin vain osan valituista tiedostoista, jolloin tarpeettomat täytyy hankalasti poistaa valinnasta. Yleinen kiertotie on luoda uusi kansio ja siirtää tiedostot sinne kopioinnin alla, mutta tämä on tehotonta ja hidasta, etenkin jos tiedostot ovat suuria. Lisäksi Ctrl+hiiren napsautus vaatii tarkkuutta, jottei menetä koko valintaa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">La sélection multiple de fichiers dans n'importe quel gestionnaire de fichiers pour les copier et les coller, n'a jamais été une expérience aussi plaisante, en particulier lorsque les fichiers ne sont pas dans un ordre continu. Souvent, lors de la sélection de fichiers en utilisant les touches « CTRL » « A » ou par l'outil de sélection, il n'est besoin que de sélectionner qu'un sous-ensemble de fichiers nécessaires parmi ceux sélectés. Bien sûr, le contournement standard est de créer un nouveau dossier et de d'insérer tous les éléments dan ce fichier avant de les copier. Mais, ceci est un processus très peu efficace et très lent si des fichiers volumineux sont à copier. De plus, une séquence « CTRL » + clic nécessite une connaissance fine du processus pour ne pas perdre la sélection entière des fichiers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Seleccionar varios ficheiros en calquera xestor de ficheiros para copiar e pegar nunca foi unha experiencia pracenteira, especialmente se os ficheiros non están en orde. A miúdo, ao seleccionar ficheiros usando Ctrl+A ou a ferramenta de selección, descubrimos que só necesitamos seleccionar unha parte dos ficheiros necesarios que seleccionamos. Isto leva á complicada operación de retirar ficheiros da selección. Por suposto, a solución máis común é crear un novo cartafol e poñer todos os elementos nel antes de copialos, pero isto é moi pouco eficiente e moi lento cando hai que copiar ficheiros grandes. Ademais Ctrl+Clic require precisión por parte do usuario para non perder toda a selección de ficheiros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">किसी भी फ़ाइल प्रबंधक में प्रतिलिपि बनाने और चिपकाने के लिए अनेक फ़ाइलों का चयन करना कभी भी सुखद अनुभव नहीं रहा है, विशेषकर जब वे इधर-उधर बिखरी हुई हों। प्रायः Ctrl+A अथवा सेलेक्शन उपकरण के माध्यम से जब हम फ़ाइलों का चयन करतें हैं, तब हम यह पाते हैं कि हमें केवल इनके उपसमुच्चय की आवश्यकता है। इसके कारण हमारे चयन से फ़ाइलों को हटाना बोझिल हो जाता है। निस्संदेह, इसका वैकल्पिक हल, एक नया फ़ोल्डर बनाना होता है, जिसमें हम सभी मनचाहे फ़ाइलें डाल सकते हैं पर बडी फ़ाइलों के लिए यह तरीका बहुत ही धीमा एवं अप्रभावी हो जाता है। साथ ही Ctrl+क्लिक से फ़ाइलों के संपूर्ण चयन को न खोने के लिए ठीक मोटर कौशल की आवश्यकता होती है।</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Pemilihan banyak file dalam semua pengelola file untuk disalin dan ditempelkan tidak pernah menjadi pengalaman yang menyenangkan, terutama jika file-file tersebut berada dalam urutan yang tidak karuan. Seringkali, ketika memilih file menggunakan Ctrl+A atau alat seleksi, kami menemukan bahwa kami hanya perlu memilih subset dari file yang diperlukan yang telah kami pilih. Ini mengarah pada operasi sulit menghapus file dari pilihan kami. Tentu saja, solusi umum adalah membuat folder baru dan meletakkan semua butir dalam folder ini sebelum disalin, tetapi ini adalah proses yang sangat tidak efisien dan sangat lambat jika file besar perlu disalin. Selain itu Ctrl+Click membutuhkan keterampilan motorik yang baik untuk tidak kehilangan seluruh pilihan file.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">La selezione di diversi file in un qualsiasi gestore di file per copiarli e incollarli non è mai stata un'esperienza piacevole, specialmente se i file non sono in ordine consecutivo. Spesso, quando si selezionano dei file usando Ctrl+A o lo strumento di selezione, ci ritroviamo a dover selezionare solo un sottoinsieme dei file richiesti che abbiamo selezionato. Questo porta ad una scomoda operazione di rimozione dei file dalla selezione. Ovviamente il trucco classico consiste nella creazione di una nuova cartella e nel copiare tutti gli elementi in questa cartella prima della copia, ma si tratta di un processo molto inefficiente e molto lento nel caso in cui debbano essere copiati dei file grandi. Inoltre Ctrl+clic richiede delle abilità manuali ben precise per non perdere l'intera selezione dei file.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">파일 관리자에서 흩어진 파일과 폴더 여러 개를 선택하는 작업은 항상 귀찮은 작업이었습니다. Ctrl+A 키나 선택 도구로 파일을 선택한 후에야 필요한 파일보다 더 많은 파일을 선택했다는 사실을 알게 됩니다. 이 상황에서 필요한 파일만 다시 선택하는 작업은 불편합니다. 새 폴더를 만들어서 복사하기 전에 모든 항목을 저장하는 식으로 둘러갈 수 있지만, 큰 파일을 복사해야 하면 매우 시간이 오래 걸리는 비효율적인 작업입니다. Ctrl+클릭을 하는 도중에 키가 잘못 눌리면 지금까지 선택한 파일이 모두 사라집니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Meerdere bestanden selecteren in elke bestandsbeheerder voor kopiëren en plakken is nooit een plezierige ervaring geweest, speciaal als de bestanden niet opeenvolgend zijn. Vaak, bij selecteren van bestanden met Ctrl+A of het selectiehulpmiddel, vinden we dat we het nodig om slechts een subset van de gewenste bestanden die we hebben geselecteerd nodig hebben. Dit leidt tot de onhandelbare bewerking van verwijderen van bestanden uit onze selectie. De algemene weg eromheen is om een nieuwe map te maken en alle items in deze map te plaatsen voor het kopiëren, maar dit is een erg inefficiënt en erg langzaam proces als grote bestanden gekopieerd moeten worden. Verder vereist Ctrl+Click fijne motoriek om niet de gehele selectie van bestanden te verliezen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Å velja fleire filer for kopiering eller flytting i ein filhandsamar har aldri vore enkelt, spesielt viss dei ikkje ligg rekkjefølgje. Når me vel filer manuelt eller med «Ctrl + A», oppdagar me gjerne at me ikkje treng alle filene, og må fjerna nokre av dei frå utvalet. Ei vanleg løysing er å laga ei mellombels mappe for å husa filene før kopiering, men dette er tregt om ein har mange eller store filer. Og med «Ctrl + klikk» kan ein lett nullstilla heile filutvalet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Wybieranie wielu plików w dowolnym programie do zarządzania plikami w celu skopiowania i wklejenia jeszcze nigdy nie było przyjemniejsze, szczególnie w przypadku, gdy pliki są w kolejności nie jeden po drugim. Często przy zaznaczaniu plików przy użyciu Ctrl+A lub narzędzia zaznaczania, zdajemy sobie sprawę, że potrzebujemy tylko części zaznaczonych plików. Prowadzi to do nieprzyjemnego usuwania plików z naszego zaznaczaenia. Oczywiście najpowszechniejszym obejściem jest stworzenie nowego katalogu i umieszczenie wszystkich elementów w tym katalogu przed skopiowaniem, lecz jest to bardzo niewydajne i powolne w przypadku kopiowania dużych plików. Ponadto Ctrl+klik wymaga dokładnych zdolności ruchowych, aby nie stracić całego zaznaczenia pliów.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">A selecção de vários ficheiros em qualquer gestor de ficheiros para copiar e colar nunca foi uma experiência agradável, especialmente se os ficheiros não estiverem juntos uns aos outros. Muitas vezes, ao seleccionar ficheiros com o Ctrl+A ou a ferramenta de selecção, descobrimos que é necessário seleccionar apenas um sub-conjunto dos ficheiros necessários entre os seleccionados. Isto conduz à operação incómoda de remover os ficheiros da nossa selecção. Obviamente, a alternativa comum é criar uma nova pasta e colocar lá todos os itens antes da cópia, mas isto é um processo muito ineficiente e lento se for necessário copiar ficheiros grandes. Para além disso, o Ctrl+click necessita de aptidões motoras adequadas para não perder toda a selecção de ficheiros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">A seleção de vários arquivos em qualquer gerenciador de arquivos para copiar e colar nunca foi uma experiência agradável, especialmente se os arquivos não estiverem em ordem sequencial. Muitas vezes, ao selecionar arquivos com Ctrl+A ou a ferramenta de seleção, descobrimos que é preciso selecionar apenas um subconjunto dos arquivos necessários entre os selecionados. Isso leva à operação incômoda de remover os arquivos da nossa seleção. Obviamente, a alternativa comum é criar uma nova pasta e colocar lá todos os itens antes da cópia, mas isso é um processo muito ineficiente e lento se for necessário copiar arquivos grandes. Além disso, o Ctrl+Clique requer habilidades motoras adequadas para não perder toda a seleção de arquivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Výber viacerých súborov v ľubovoľnom správcovi súborov na kopírovanie a vkladanie nebol nikdy príjemným zážitkom, najmä ak sú súbory v nesúvislom poradí. Pri výbere súborov pomocou klávesov Ctrl + A alebo nástroja na výber často zistíme, že musíme vybrať iba podmnožinu požadovaných súborov, ktoré sme vybrali. To vedie k ťažkopádnemu odstraňovaniu súborov z nášho výberu. Samozrejme, spoločným riešením je vytvoriť nový priečinok a vložiť všetky položky do tohto priečinka pred kopírovaním, je to však veľmi neefektívny a veľmi pomalý proces, ak je potrebné kopírovať veľké súbory. Ctrl + Click navyše vyžaduje jemné motorické zručnosti, aby sa nestratil celý výber súborov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Izbira več datotek v katerem koli upravitelju datotek za kopiranje in lepljenje ni bila nikoli prijetna izkušnja, še posebej, če so datoteke v neprekinjenem vrstnem redu. Pogosto pri izbiri datotek s Ctrl+A ali izbirnim orodjem ugotovimo, da moramo izbrati samo podmnožico potrebnih datotek, ki smo jih izbrali. To vodi v neprijetno odstranjevanje datotek iz našega izbora. Seveda je skupno rešitev ustvariti novo mapo in vse elemente v to mapo postaviti pred kopiranjem, vendar je to zelo neučinkovit in zelo počasen postopek, če je treba kopirati velike datoteke. Poleg tega Ctrl+Klik zahteva fine motorične spretnosti, da ne izgubite celotnega izbora datotek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Att markera flera fler i någon filhanterare för att kopiera och klistra in har aldrig varit en trevlig upplevelse, i synnerhet om filerna inte är i följdordning. Ofta när man markerar filer med Ctrl+A eller markeringsverktyg, märker man att man enbart måste välja ut en delmängd av filerna som har blivit markerade. Det leder till en tungrodd operation för att ta bort filer från markeringen. Det vanliga sättet att gå runt det är förstås att skapa en ny katalog och placera alla objekt i den innan kopiering, men det är en mycket ineffektiv och långsam process om stora filer behöver kopieras. Dessutom kräver Ctrl+klick bra motoriska färdigheter för att inte förlora hela filmarkeringen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Dosya kopyalama ve yapıştırma için herhangi bir dosya yöneticisindeki birden fazla dosyayı seçmek, özellikle dosyalar ın sürekli olmayan bir sırada olduğunda hoş bir deneyim yaşatmaz. Çoğu zaman, Ctrl+A veya seçim aracı kullanarak dosyaları seçerken, seçmiş olduğumuz gerekli dosyaların yalnızca bir alt kümesini seçmemiz gerektiğini görürüz. Bu, dosyalarımızı seçimimizden kaldırmanın hantallaşmasına yol açar. Elbette, ortak bir geçici çözüm, yeni bir klasör oluşturmak ve kopyalamadan önce bu klasördeki tüm ögeleri içine koymaktır; ancak büyük dosyaların kopyalanması gerekiyorsa bu çok verimsiz ve çok yavaş bir işlemdir. Üstelik Ctrl +Tıklama, tüm dosya seçimini kaybetmemek için iyi motor becerilerini gerektirir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Позначення декількох файлів у програмі для керування файлами ніколи не було зовсім простою справою, особливо якщо файли у наборі розташовано у різних місцях екрана. Часто після позначення файлів за допомогою комбінації клавіш Ctrl+A або засобів позначення виявляється, що потрібні нам файли є лише підмножиною позначеного набору. Звичайно ж, можна створити нову теку і розмістити у ній всі потрібні об’єкти до копіювання, але це значно ускладнює процес, якщо відбувається копіювання великих файлів. Крім того, використання комбінації Ctrl+клацання потребує певних навичок для того, щоб випадково не скасувати позначення усього раніше позначеного набору файлів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxSelecting multiple files in any file manager for copying and pasting has never been a pleasant experience, especially if the files are in a non-continuous order. Often, when selecting files using Ctrl+A or the selection tool, we find that we need to select only a subset of the required files we have selected. This leads to the unwieldy operation of removing files from our selection. Of course, the common workaround is to create a new folder and to put all the items in this folder prior to copying, but this is a very inefficient and very slow process if large files need to be copied. Moreover Ctrl+Click requires fine motor skills to not lose the entire selection of files.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">在任何文件管理器中，复制粘贴多个文件的体验都十分糟糕，文件顺序不连续时更甚。当我们使用 Ctrl+A 或选择工具选择文件时，一般只需要选择其中的一小部分。在这种情况下，取消选择就会变得十分复杂。当然，最常见的变通办法是在复制前先创建一个新文件夹，并将已选择的文件全放进去。但如果需要复制大量文件，这种过程会变得既低效又漫长；此外，按住 Ctrl 点击也需要精准的鼠标移动技巧，才不会点错而导致已选择的文件被取消选择。</p>
    <p>This is project has a novel solution to this problem. This adds virtual folder support in all KIO applications, where the links to files and folders can be temporarily saved for a session. The files and folders are "staged" on this virtual folder. Files can be added to this by using all the regular file management operations such as Move, Copy and Paste, or by drag and drop. Hence, complex file operations such as moving files across many devices can be made easy by staging the operation before performing it.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">هذا المشروع لديه حل جديد لهذه المشكلة. يضيف هذا دعمًا لمجلد افتراضي في جميع تطبيقات KIO ، حيث يمكن حفظ الروابط إلى الملفات والمجلدات مؤقتًا للجلسة. يتم "تنظيم" الملفات والمجلدات على هذا المجلد الافتراضي. يمكن إضافة الملفات إلى هذا باستخدام جميع عمليات إدارة الملفات العادية مثل النقل والنسخ واللصق ، أو بالسحب والإفلات. وبالتالي ، يمكن تسهيل عمليات الملفات المعقدة مثل نقل الملفات عبر العديد من الأجهزة من خلال تنظيم العملية قبل تنفيذها.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Aquest projecte té una solució nova a aquest problema. Afegeix la implementació de carpetes virtuals a totes les aplicacions KIO, a on els enllaços a fitxers i carpetes es poden desar temporalment durant una sessió. Els fitxers i carpetes es «reserven» en aquesta carpeta virtual. Els fitxers s'hi poden afegir usant totes les operacions normals de la gestió de fitxers com moure, copiar i enganxar, o arrossegar i deixar anar. Per tant, les operacions complexes de fitxer com moure fitxers per diversos dispositius es pot facilitar reservant l'operació abans de portar-la a terme.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Este projecte té una solució nova a este problema. Afig la implementació de carpetes virtuals a totes les aplicacions KIO, a on els enllaços cap a fitxers i carpetes es poden guardar temporalment durant una sessió. Els fitxers i carpetes es «reserven» en esta carpeta virtual. Els fitxers s'hi poden afegir utilitzant totes les operacions normals de la gestió de fitxers com moure, copiar i apegar, o arrossegar i deixar anar. Per tant, les operacions complexes de fitxer com moure fitxers per diversos dispositius es pot facilitar reservant l'operació abans de portar-la a terme.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Dette projekt har en anderledes løsning på problemet. Det tilføjer understøttelse af virtuelle mapper i alle KIO-programmer, hvor linkene til filer og mapper midlertidigt kan gemmes for en session. Filerne og mapperne er "iscenesat" på den virtuelle mappe. Filer kan tilføjes til den ved at bruge alle de normale filhåndteringshandlinger såsom Flyt, Kopiér, Indsæt eller med træk-og-slip. Derfor kan komplekse filhandlinger, såsom at flytte filer på tværs af mange enheder gøres let, ved at iscenesætte handlingen inden den udføres.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Αυτό το έργο αποτελεί μια καινοτόμα λύση αε αυτό το πρόβλημα. Προσθέτει υποστήριξη εικονικών φακέλων σε όλες τις KIO εφαρμογές, όπου δεσμοί σε αρχεία και φακέλους αποθηκεύονται προσωρινά για μια συνεδρία. Τα αρχεία και οι φάκελοι «μπαίνουν στην άκρη» σε αυτόν τον εικονικό φάκελο. Αρχεία μπορούν να προστεθούν σε αυτόν με χρήση όλων των συνηθισμένων λειτουργιών διαχείρισης αρχείων όπως μετακίνηση, αντιγραφή και επικόλληση ή με έλξη και εναπόθεση. Άρα, σύνθετες λειτουργίες με αρχεία όπως η μεταφορά τους ανάμεσα σε πολλές συσκευές διευκολύνεται βάζοντας στην άκρη τη λειτουργία πριν αυτή να εκτελεστεί.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">This is project has a novel solution to this problem. This adds virtual folder support in all KIO applications, where the links to files and folders can be temporarily saved for a session. The files and folders are "staged" on this virtual folder. Files can be added to this by using all the regular file management operations such as Move, Copy and Paste, or by drag and drop. Hence, complex file operations such as moving files across many devices can be made easy by staging the operation before performing it.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Este proyecto proporciona una solución innovadora para este problema implementando carpetas virtuales a todas las aplicaciones que usan KIO, donde los enlaces a los archivos y carpetas se pueden guardar de forma temporal para una sesión. Los archivos y carpetas se «montan» en esta carpeta virtual. Puede añadir archivos usando las operaciones de gestión de archivos habituales, como mover, copiar y pegar, o arrastrar y soltar. Por consiguiente, puede realizar con facilidad operaciones de archivos complejas, como moverlos entre varios dispositivos, almacenando temporalmente la operación antes de realizarla.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Meie projekt pakub probleemile välja uudse lahenduse. See lisab virtuaalse kataloogi toetuse kõigile KIO-võimekusega rakendustele, mis lubab seansi ajaks ajutiselt salvestada linke failidele ja kataloogidele. Failid ja kataloogid jäävad virtuaalses kataloogis nii-öelda "ootele". Faile saab sinna lisada nii tavaliste failihaldustegevustega, nagu näiteks liigutamine, kopeerimine ja asetamine, aga ka lohistades. Nii muutuvad isegi sellised keerukad operatsioonid, nagu näiteks paljude failide liigutamine eri seadmete vahel, päris lihtsaks, kui seada enne tegelikku toimingut kõik vajalik ühte kohta valmis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Proiektu honek arazoari irtenbide berri bat ematen dio. KIO aplikazio guztietan alegiazko karpeten euskarria gehitzen du, non fitxategien eta karpeten estekak aldi baterako gorde daitezkeen saioak iraun bitartean. Fitxategiak eta karpetak alegiazko karpeta honetan «antolatuta» daude. Fitxategiak honetara gehitu daitezke fitxategi kudeaketa eragiketa erregular guztiak erabiliz, mugitu, kopiatu eta itsatsi, edo arrastatu eta jaregin.  Hori dela eta, eragiketa korapilatsuak, fitxategiak gailu ezberdinen artean mugitzea adibidez, erraz egin daitezke eragiketa gauzatu aurretik haiek antolatuz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tämä projekti on uusi ratkaisu ongelmaan. Se lisää kaikkiin KIO-sovelluksiin tuen virtuaalikansioille, jonne tiedostoja ja kansioita voi istunnon ajaksi väliaikaisesti tallentaa. Tässä virtuaalikansiossa tiedostot ja kansiot ovat ”välivaiheessa”. Niitä voi viedä sinne tavallisin tiedostonhallintatoimenpiten (siirto, kopiointi, liittäminen, veto ja pudotus). Monimutkaisia tiedostotoimintoja kuten tiedostojen siirtämistä laitteelta toiselle voi näin helpottaa luomalla toimintoon välivaiheen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ce projet propose une solution nouvelle à ce problème. Il ajoute la prise en charge d'un dossier virtuel dans tous les applications de KIO, où les liens vers les fichiers peuvent être enregistrés temporairement durant une session. Les fichiers et les dossiers sont « instrumentés » sur ce dossier virtuel. Les fichiers peuvent lui être ajoutés en utilisant les opérations classiques de gestion de fichiers comme Déplacer, Copier et Coller ou par un glisser / déposer. Ainsi, les opérations complexes sur les fichiers, tel que le déplacement de fichiers vers plusieurs périphériques, peuvent être rendus facile en instrumentant l'opération avant d'exécuter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Este proxecto fornece unha nova solución para este problema. Engade compatibilidade con cartafoles virtuais ás aplicacións que usen KIO, onde poder gardar as ligazóns a ficheiros e cartafoles de maneira temporal, gardados durante a sesión. Os ficheiros e cartafoles “resérvanse” neste cartafol virtual, ao que se lle poden engadir ficheiros usando as operacións habituais de xestión de ficheiros como mover, copiar ou pegar, ou arrastrando e soltando. Deste modo, operacións complexas de ficheiros como mover ficheiros de moitos dispositivos poden simplificarse gardando as operacións na reserva antes de executalas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">यह परियोजना के पास इस समस्या का एक परिवर्तनात्‍मक समाधान है। यह सभी केआईओ अनुप्रयोगों में आभासी फ़ोल्डर का समर्थन जोड़ देता है, जहाँ फाइलों तथा फ़ोल्डरों की कड़ियाँ अस्थायी रूप से सहेजी जाती हैं। इस वर्चुअल फोल्डर पर फाइलें और फोल्डर "स्टेज" होते हैं। सभी नियमित फ़ाइल प्रबंधन कार्यों जैसे फ़ाइल हिलाने, प्रतिलिपि बनाने और चिपकाने, या ड्रैग एंड ड्रॉप का उपयोग करके इसमें फ़ाइलें जोड़ी जा सकती हैं।  इसमें हम साधारण तरीकों से फ़ाइल डाल सकते हैं, इसलिए जटिल कार्य जैसे की कई उपकरणों में फ़ाइल डालना अब सरल हो गया है।</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Projek ini memiliki solusi baru untuk masalah ini. Ini menambahkan dukungan folder virtual di semua aplikasi KIO, dimana tautan ke file dan folder dapat disimpan sementara untuk satu sesi. File dan folder "staged" pada folder virtual ini. File dapat ditambahkan ke sini dengan menggunakan semua operasi pengelola file biasa seperti Pindah, Salin, dan Tempel, atau dengan seret dan taruh. Oleh karena itu, operasi file yang kompleks seperti memindahkan file di banyak peranti dapat dipermudah dengan mengatur operasi sebelum melakukannya.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Questo progetto presenta una soluzione originale al problema. Aggiunge il supporto alle cartelle virtuali in tutte le applicazioni KIO, in cui è possibile salvare temporaneamente i collegamenti a file e cartelle per una sessione. I file e le cartelle sono messe da parte («staged») in questa cartella virtuale. I file possono essere aggiunti ad essa usando tutte le normali operazioni di gestione dei file come Sposta, Copia e Incolla, o tramite trascinamento. Perciò tutte le operazioni complesse sui file come lo spostamento di file tra dispositivi diversi possono essere rese semplici tramite uno staging dell'operazione prima di eseguirla.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">이 프로젝트는 이 문제를 해결하는 방안을 제시합니다. 모든 KIO 프로그램에 가상 폴더 지원을 추가해서 현재 세션에서 사용할 수 있는 파일과 폴더의 임시 링크를 저장합니다. 파일과 폴더는 이 가상 폴더에 "임시로 저장"됩니다. 이동, 복사, 붙여넣기, 드래그 앤 드롭 등 일반적인 모든 파일 관리 작업으로 여기에 파일을 추가할 수 있습니다. 여러 장치로 파일을 이동하는 등의 복잡한 파일 작업은 실제 작업을 수행하기 전에 임시 폴더에 저장해서 쉽게 해결할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Dit project heeft een vernieuwende oplossing tot dit probleem. Dit voegt ondersteuning voor virtuele mappen toe aan alle KIO-toepassingen, waar de koppelingen naar bestanden en mappen tijdelijk in opgeslagen kunnen worden voor een sessie. De bestanden en mappen worden "staged" in deze virtuele map. Bestanden kunnen hieraan worden toegevoegd door alle reguliere bewerkingen bij bestandsbeheer zoals Verplaatsen, Kopiëren en Plakken of door slepen en loslaten. Complexe bestandsbewerkingen zoals verplaatsen van bestanden over vele apparaten kan gemakkelijk gemaakt worden door "staging" van de bewerking alvorens deze uit te voeren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Dette prosjektet har ei original løysing på problemet. Det legg til ei virtuell mappe i alle program som brukar KIO, der lenkjer til filer og mapper kan lagrast mellombels (ut økta). Du kan bruka alle vanlege filoperasjonar, som kopiering, flytting og innliming, anten med snøggtastar eller dra-og-slepp. Komplekse filoperasjonar, der du for eksempel skal flytta filer på tvers av mange einingar, vert på denne måten mykje enklare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Ten projekt ma nowe rozwiązanie na przedstawiony problem. Dodaje on obsługę wirutalnych katalogów we wszystkich aplikacjach KIO, w których odnośniki do plików i katalogów można tymczasowo zapisać dla sesji. Pliki i katalogi są "dobierane" do tego wirtualnego katalogu. Pliki można dodawać wykorzystując wszystkie zwyczajne działania na plikach takie jak przenieś, kopiuj, wklej lub przeciągnij. Dzięki temu, złożone działania na plikach takie jak przenoszenie plików z wielu urządzeń jest łatwiejsze poprzez przygotowanie działania przed jego wykonaniem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Este projecto tem uma solução nova para este problema. Adiciona o suporte para pastas virtuais em todas as aplicações do KIO, onde as ligações aos ficheiros e pastas podem ser gravadas temporariamente para uma dada sessão. Os ficheiros e pastas ficam "preparados" nesta pasta virtual. Poderá adicionar ficheiros à mesma se usar todas as operações normais de gestão de ficheiros, como o Mover, o Copiar e o Colar ou ainda por arrastamento. Deste modo, as operações complexas com ficheiros, como a mudança de posição dos ficheiros entre vários dispositivos pode ser feita facilmente se preparar a operação antes de a executar propriamente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Este projeto tem uma nova solução para esse problema. Adiciona o suporte a pastas virtuais em todos os aplicativos do KIO, onde os links com os arquivos e pastas podem ser salvos temporariamente para apenas uma sessão. Os arquivos e pastas ficam "preparados" nessa pasta virtual. Os arquivos podem ser adicionados à mesma ao usar qualquer uma das operações normais de gerenciamento de arquivos, como mover, copiar e colar, ou a ação de arrastar e soltar. Desse modo, as operações complexas com arquivos, como a movimentação entre vários dispositivos pode ser feita facilmente com o preparo da operação antes de sua execução.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Toto je projekt, ktorý má nové riešenie tohto problému. Pridáva podporu virtuálnych priečinkov do všetkých aplikácií KIO, kde je možné odkazy na súbory a priečinky dočasne uložiť do sedenia. Súbory a priečinky sú v tomto virtuálnom priečinku „predpripravené“. Súbory je možné pridať pomocou všetkých bežných operácií správy súborov, ako je presun, kopírovanie a vloženie, alebo pretiahnutím. Zložité operácie so súbormi, ako napr. presúvanie súborov naprieč mnohými zariadeniami, je preto možné jednoduchým spôsobom predpripraviť pred ich vykonaním.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Ta projekt ima novo rešitev tega problema. To doda podporo za navidezno mapo v vseh aplikacijah KIO, kjer se lahko povezave do datotek in map začasno shranijo za sejo. Datoteke in mape so "uprizorjene" v tej virtualni mapi. Datoteke lahko k temu dodate z uporabo vseh običajnih operacij upravljanja datotek, kot so premikanje, kopiranje in lepljenje, ali z vlečenjem in spustitvijo. Zato lahko zapletene datoteke z operacijami, kot je premikanje datotek po številnih napravah, olajšate tako, da operacijo nadaljujete pred izvedbo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Detta är ett projekt som har en originell lösning på problemet. Det lägger till stöd för virtuella kataloger i alla KIO-program, där länkar till filer och kataloger kan sparas tillfälligt under en session. Filerna och katalogerna "förbereds" i denna virtuella katalog. Filer kan läggas till i den genom att använda de vanliga filhanteringsåtgärderna såsom flytta, kopiera och klistra in, eller med drag och släpp. Därigenom kan komplexa åtgärder såsom att flytta filer mellan många enheter göras enkla genom att förbereda åtgärden innan den utförs.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Proje bu soruna yeni bir çözüm getiriyor. Bu, dosya ve klasörlere olan bağlantılar geçici olarak bir oturum için kaydedilebilen tüm KIO uygulamalarında sanal klasör desteği ekler. Dosyalar ve klasörler bu sanal klasörde "aşamalı" haldedirler. Dosyaları, Taşı, Kopyala ve Yapıştır gibi tüm normal dosya yönetimi işlemlerini kullanarak veya sürükleyip bırakarak ekleyebilirsiniz. Bu nedenle, birçok aygıt arasında dosya taşıma gibi karmaşık dosya işlemleri işlemi gerçekleştirmeden önce işlemi aşamalaştırarakkolaylaştırabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Цей проєкт пропонує новітнє вирішення проблеми. Програмними засобами створюється віртуальна тека в усіх програмах із підтримкою KIO. У цій теці протягом сеансу роботи можуть тимчасово зберігатися посилання на файли і теки. Ці файли і теки складають «стос» віртуальної теки. До стосу можна додавати нові запис за допомогою звичайних операцій із керування файлами — пересування, копіювання та вставлення — або за допомогою перетягування зі скиданням. Таким чином, складні дії з файлами, зокрема пересування файлів між багатьма пристроями можна доволі просто виконати, розмістивши файли у стосі до виконання копіювання.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThis is project has a novel solution to this problem. This adds virtual folder support in all KIO applications, where the links to files and folders can be temporarily saved for a session. The files and folders are "staged" on this virtual folder. Files can be added to this by using all the regular file management operations such as Move, Copy and Paste, or by drag and drop. Hence, complex file operations such as moving files across many devices can be made easy by staging the operation before performing it.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">此项目为这类问题提供了一个全新的解决方案。它添加了一个所有 KIO 应用程序都支持的虚拟文件夹，并将文件和文件夹的链接临时储存到会话中。会话中的文件和文件夹都会被暂存到虚拟文件夹内，而常规的文件管理操作 (如移动、复制和粘贴或是直接拖动) 都会将文件添加到此文件夹。因此，只要在执行前暂存操作，就能轻易做到复杂的文件操作 (如跨设备移动文件)。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=filestash</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=filestash</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kio-stash/kio-stash.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>System</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">folder-temp</icon>
</component>
