<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component>
  <id>org.kde.filestash.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <name>FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">PrzechowalniaPlików</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Filestash</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">FileStash</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxFileStashxx</name>
  <summary>A lightweight solution for virtual folder support in KDE Applications. </summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Una solució lleugera per permetre carpetes virtuals a les aplicacions KDE.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Una solució lleugera per permetre carpetes virtuals a les aplicacions KDE.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">En letvægtsløsning til understøttelse af virtuelle mapper i KDE-programmer.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Eine leichtgewichtige Lösung für die Unterstützung von virtuellen Ordner in KDE-Anwendungen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Μια ελαφριά λύση υποστήριξης εικονικών φακέλων στις KDE Εφαρμογές.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">A lightweight solution for virtual folder support in KDE Applications.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Una solución liviana para implementar carpetas virtuales en las aplicaciones de KDE.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Kevyt KDE Applications -virtuaalikansiotukiratkaisu.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Unha solución sinxela para fornecer compatibilidade con cartafoles virtuais en aplicativos de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Solusi ringan untuk dukungan folder virtual di KDE Applications.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">KDE 프로그램의 가벼운 가상 폴더 지원입니다.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een lichtgewicht oplossing voor ondersteuning van virtuele mappen in KDE Applications.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Lekkie rozwiązanie obsługi wirtualnych katalogów w Aplikacjach KDE.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Uma solução leve para o suporte de pastas virtuais nas Aplicações do KDE.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Jednoduché riešenie pre podporu virtuálnych priečinkov v KDE aplikáciách.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">En lättviktig lösning för stöd av virtuella kataloger i KDE-program.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">KDE Uygulamalarında, sanal klasör desteği için hafif bir çözüm.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Невибагливий до ресурсів інструмент підтримки віртуальних тек у програмах KDE.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxA lightweight solution for virtual folder support in KDE Applications.xx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Selecting multiple files in any file manager for copying and pasting has never been a pleasant experience, especially if the files are in a non-continuous order. Often, when selecting files using Ctrl+A or the selection tool, we find that we need to select only a subset of the required files we have selected. This leads to the unwieldy operation of removing files from our selection. Of course, the common workaround is to create a new folder and to put all the items in this folder prior to copying, but this is a very inefficient and very slow process if large files need to be copied. Moreover Ctrl+Click requires fine motor skills to not lose the entire selection of files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">La selecció de diversos fitxers en qualsevol gestor de fitxers per copiar i enganxar mai ha estat una experiència agradable, especialment si els fitxers estan en un ordre no contigu. Sovint, en seleccionar fitxers usant Ctrl+A o l'eina de selecció, ens trobem que cal seleccionar només un subconjunt dels fitxers requerits que hem seleccionat. Això porta a la tasca pesada d'eliminar fitxers de la selecció. Per descomptat, l'alternativa més freqüent és crear una carpeta nova i posar tots els elements en aquesta carpeta abans de copiar-hi, però això és un procés molt ineficient i molt lent si cal copiar fitxers grans. A més, Ctrl+Clic requereix habilitats motores fines per no perdre tota la selecció de fitxers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">La selecció de diversos fitxers en qualsevol gestor de fitxers per copiar i enganxar mai ha estat una experiència agradable, especialment si els fitxers estan en un ordre no contigu. Sovint, en seleccionar fitxers usant Ctrl+A o l'eina de selecció, ens trobem que cal seleccionar només un subconjunt dels fitxers requerits que hem seleccionat. Això porta a la tasca pesada d'eliminar fitxers de la selecció. Per descomptat, l'alternativa més freqüent és crear una carpeta nova i posar tots els elements en aquesta carpeta abans de copiar-hi, però això és un procés molt ineficient i molt lent si cal copiar fitxers grans. A més, Ctrl+Clic requereix habilitats motores fines per no perdre tota la selecció de fitxers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">At vælge flere filer i enhver filhåndtering til kopiering og indsættelse har aldrig været en behagelig oplevelse, specielt hvis filerne ikke er i fortløbende rækkefølge. Oftest når du vælger filer med Ctrl+A eller markeringsværktøjet, så finder du ud af at du kun har brug for en del af de valgte filer. Det fører til den besværlige handlinger det er at fjerne filer fra markeringen. Man kan selvfølgelig bruge den almindelige løsning med at oprette en ny mappe og ligge alle elementerne i mappen inden kopiering, men det er en meget ineffektiv og meget langsom proces hvis der er store filer som skal kopieres. Desuden kræver Ctrl+klik de nødvendige finmotoriske evner for ikke at miste hele filmarkeringen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Η επιλονή πολλών αρχείων σε οποιονδήποτε διαχειριστή αρχείων για αντιγραφή και επικόλληση δεν είναι ποτέ μια ευχάριστη εμπειρία, ειδικά αν τα αρχεία δεν είναι συνεχόμενα. Συχνά, όταν επιλέγουμε αρχεία με το Ctrl+A ή με το εργαλείο επιλογής, παρατηρούμε ότι χρειαζόμαστε μόνο ένα υποσύνολο από τα αρχεία που έχουμε επιλέξει. Αυτό οδηγεί στην άβολη διαδικασία να διαγράψουμε αρχεία από τα επιλεγμένα. Βέβαια η συνήθης λύση είναι να δημιουργήσουμε έναν νέο φάκελο και να βάλουμε όλα τα αντικείμενα εκεί πριν τα αντιγράψουμε, αλλά αυτή είναι μια πολύ αναποτελεσματική και αργή διεργασία αν απαιτείται η αντιγραφή μεγάλων αρχείων. Επιπλέον το Ctrl+Click απαιτεί λεπτές κινητικές δεξιότητες ώστε να μην αναιρεθεί όλη η επιλογή των αρχείων.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Selecting multiple files in any file manager for copying and pasting has never been a pleasant experience, especially if the files are in a non-continuous order. Often, when selecting files using Ctrl+A or the selection tool, we find that we need to select only a subset of the required files we have selected. This leads to the unwieldy operation of removing files from our selection. Of course, the common workaround is to create a new folder and to put all the items in this folder prior to copying, but this is a very inefficient and very slow process if large files need to be copied. Moreover Ctrl+Click requires fine motor skills to not lose the entire selection of files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">La selección de múltiples archivos en cualquier gestor de archivos para copiarlos y pegarlos nunca ha sido una experiencia agradable, especialmente si los archivos no son consecutivos. A menudo, cuando se seleccionan archivos usando Ctrl+A o la herramienta de selección, nos damos cuenta de que solo necesitamos seleccionar un subconjunto de los archivos que ya hemos seleccionado. Esto conduce a la poco manejable operación de eliminar archivos de la selección. Por supuesto, la solución común consiste en crear una nueva carpeta y colocar en ella todos los elementos antes de copiarlos, aunque esto es un proceso muy lento y poco eficiente si es necesario copiar archivos grandes. Además, Ctrl+clic necesita de habilidades motoras precisas para no perder toda la selección de archivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Useamman tiedoston valitseminen kopioitavaksi tai liitettäväksi ei milloinkaan missään tiedostonhallintaohjelmassa ole ollut helppoa, etenkään jos tiedostot eivät ole peräkkäin. Usein valittuaan tiedostoja Ctrl+A:lla tai valintatyökalulla huomaa, että tarvitseekin vain osan valituista tiedostoista, jolloin tarpeettomat täytyy hankalasti poistaa valinnasta. Yleinen kiertotie on luoda uusi kansio ja siirtää tiedostot sinne kopioinnin alla, mutta tämä on tehotonta ja hidasta, etenkin jos tiedostot ovat suuria. Lisäksi Ctrl+hiiren napsautus vaatii tarkkuutta, jottei menetä koko valintaa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Seleccionar varios ficheiros en calquera xestor de ficheiros para copiar e pegar nunca foi unha experiencia pracenteira, especialmente se os ficheiros non están en orde. A miúdo, ao seleccionar ficheiros usando Ctrl+A ou a ferramenta de selección, descubrimos que só necesitamos seleccionar unha parte dos ficheiros necesarios que seleccionamos. Isto leva á complicada operación de retirar ficheiros da selección. Por suposto, a solución máis común é crear un novo cartafol e poñer todos os elementos nel antes de copialos, pero isto é moi pouco eficiente e moi lento cando hai que copiar ficheiros grandes. Ademais Ctrl+Clic require precisión por parte do usuario para non perder toda a selección de ficheiros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Memilih banyak file dalam semua pengelola file untuk disalin dan ditempelkan tidak pernah menjadi pengalaman yang menyenangkan, terutama jika file-file tersebut berada dalam urutan yang tidak karuan. Seringkali, ketika memilih file menggunakan Ctrl+A atau alat seleksi, kami menemukan bahwa kami hanya perlu memilih subset dari file yang diperlukan yang telah kami pilih. Ini mengarah pada operasi sulit menghapus file dari pilihan kami. Tentu saja, solusi umum adalah membuat folder baru dan meletakkan semua item dalam folder ini sebelum disalin, tetapi ini adalah proses yang sangat tidak efisien dan sangat lambat jika file besar perlu disalin. Selain itu Ctrl+Click membutuhkan keterampilan motorik yang baik untuk tidak kehilangan seluruh pilihan file.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">파일 관리자에서 여러 개의 흩어진 파일과 폴더를 선택하는 작업은 항상 귀찮은 작업이었습니다. Ctrl+A 키나 선택 도구로 파일을 선택한 후에야 필요한 파일보다 더 많은 파일을 선택했다는 사실을 알게 됩니다. 이 상황에서 필요한 파일만 다시 선택하는 작업은 불편합니다. 새 폴더를 만들어서 복사하기 전에 모든 항목을 저장하는 식으로 둘러갈 수 있지만, 큰 파일을 복사해야 하면 매우 시간이 오래 걸리는 비효율적인 작업입니다. Ctrl+클릭을 하는 도중에 키가 잘못 눌리면 지금까지 선택한 파일이 모두 사라집니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Meerdere bestanden selecteren in elke bestandsbeheerder voor kopiëren en plakken is nooit een plezierige ervaring geweest, speciaal als de bestanden niet opeenvolgend zijn. Vaak, bij selecteren van bestanden met Ctrl+A of het selectiehulpmiddel, vinden we dat we het nodig om slechts een subset van de gewenste bestanden die we hebben geselecteerd nodig hebben. Dit leidt tot de onhandelbare bewerking van verwijderen van bestanden uit onze selectie. De algemene weg eromheen is om een nieuwe map te maken en alle items in deze map te plaatsen voor het kopiëren, maar dit is een erg inefficiënt en erg langzaam proces als grote bestanden gekopieerd moeten worden. Verder vereist Ctrl+Click fijne motoriek om niet de gehele selectie van bestanden te verliezen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Wybieranie wielu plików w dowolnym programie do zarządzania plikami w celu skopiowania i wklejenia jeszcze nigdy nie było przyjemniejsze, szczególnie w przypadku, gdy pliki są w kolejności nie jeden po drugim. Często przy zaznaczaniu plików przy użyciu Ctrl+A lub narzędzia zaznaczania, zdajemy sobie sprawę, że potrzebujemy tylko części zaznaczonych plików. Prowadzi to do nieprzyjemnego usuwania plików z naszego zaznaczaenia. Oczywiście najpowszechniejszym obejściem jest stworzenie nowego katalogu i umieszczenie wszystkich elementów w tym katalogu przed skopiowaniem, lecz jest to bardzo niewydajne i powolne w przypadku kopiowania dużych plików. Ponadto Ctrl+klik wymaga dokładnych zdolności ruchowych, aby nie stracić całego zaznaczenia pliów.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">A selecção de vários ficheiros em qualquer gestor de ficheiros para copiar e colar nunca foi uma experiência agradável, especialmente se os ficheiros não estiverem juntos uns aos outros. Muitas vezes, ao seleccionar ficheiros com o Ctrl+A ou a ferramenta de selecção, descobrimos que é necessário seleccionar apenas um sub-conjunto dos ficheiros necessários entre os seleccionados. Isto conduz à operação incómoda de remover os ficheiros da nossa selecção. Obviamente, a alternativa comum é criar uma nova pasta e colocar lá todos os itens antes da cópia, mas isto é um processo muito ineficiente e lento se for necessário copiar ficheiros grandes. Para além disso, o Ctrl+click necessita de aptidões motoras adequadas para não perder toda a selecção de ficheiros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Att markera flera fler i någon filhanterare för att kopiera och klistra in har aldrig varit en trevlig upplevelse, i synnerhet om filerna inte är i följdordning. Ofta när man markerar filer med Ctrl+A eller markeringsverktyg, märker man att man enbart måste välja ut en delmängd av filerna som har blivit markerade. Det leder till en tungrodd operation för att ta bort filer från markeringen. Det vanliga sättet att gå runt det är förstås att skapa en ny katalog och placera alla objekt i den innan kopiering, men det är en mycket ineffektiv och långsam process om stora filer behöver kopieras. Dessutom kräver Ctrl+klick bra motoriska färdigheter för att inte förlora hela filmarkeringen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Dosya kopyalama ve yapıştırma için herhangi bir dosya yöneticisindeki birden fazla dosyayı seçmek, özellikle dosyalar ın sürekli olmayan bir sırada olduğunda hoş bir deneyim yaşanmamıştı. Çoğu zaman, Ctrl + A veya seçim aracı kullanarak dosyaları seçerken, seçmiş olduğumuz gerekli dosyaların yalnızca bir alt kümesini seçmemiz gerektiğini görürürüz. Bu, dosyalarımızı seçimimizden kaldırmanın hantal bir işlemesine yol açar. Elbette, ortak bir geçici çözüm, yeni bir klasör oluşturmak ve kopyalamadan önce bu klasördeki tüm öğeleri içine koymaktır, ancak büyük dosyaların kopyalanması gerekiyorsa, bu çok verimsiz ve çok yavaş bir işlemdir. Üstelik Ctrl + Tıklama, tüm dosya seçimini kaybetmemek için iyi motor becerileri gerektirir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Позначення декількох файлів у програмі для керування файлами ніколи не було зовсім простою справою, особливо якщо файли у наборі розташовано у різних місцях екрана. Часто після позначення файлів за допомогою комбінації клавіш Ctrl+A або засобів позначення виявляється, що потрібні нам файли є лише підмножиною позначеного набору. Звичайно ж, можна створити нову теку і розмістити у ній всі потрібні об’єкти до копіювання, але це значно ускладнює процес, якщо відбувається копіювання великих файлів. Крім того, використання комбінації Ctrl+клацання потребує певних навичок для того, щоб випадково не скасувати позначення усього раніше позначеного набору файлів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxSelecting multiple files in any file manager for copying and pasting has never been a pleasant experience, especially if the files are in a non-continuous order. Often, when selecting files using Ctrl+A or the selection tool, we find that we need to select only a subset of the required files we have selected. This leads to the unwieldy operation of removing files from our selection. Of course, the common workaround is to create a new folder and to put all the items in this folder prior to copying, but this is a very inefficient and very slow process if large files need to be copied. Moreover Ctrl+Click requires fine motor skills to not lose the entire selection of files.xx</p>
    <p>This is project has a novel solution to this problem. This adds virtual folder support in all KIO applications, where the links to files and folders can be temporarily saved for a session. The files and folders are "staged" on this virtual folder. Files can be added to this by using all the regular file management operations such as Move, Copy and Paste, or by drag and drop. Hence, complex file operations such as moving files across many devices can be made easy by staging the operation before performing it.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Aquest projecte té una solució nova a aquest problema. Afegeix la implementació de carpetes virtuals a totes les aplicacions KIO, a on els enllaços a fitxers i carpetes es poden desar temporalment durant una sessió. Els fitxers i carpetes es «reserven» en aquesta carpeta virtual. Els fitxers es poden afegir-hi usant totes les operacions normals de gestió de fitxers com moure, copiar i enganxar, o arrossegar i deixar anar. Per tant, les operacions complexes de fitxer com moure fitxes per diversos dispositius es pot facilitar reservant l'operació abans de portar-la a terme.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Aquest projecte té una solució nova a aquest problema. Afig la implementació de carpetes virtuals a totes les aplicacions KIO, a on els enllaços a fitxers i carpetes es poden guardar temporalment durant una sessió. Els fitxers i carpetes es «reserven» en aquesta carpeta virtual. Els fitxers es poden afegir-hi usant totes les operacions normals de gestió de fitxers com moure, copiar i enganxar, o arrossegar i deixar anar. Per tant, les operacions complexes de fitxer com moure fitxes per diversos dispositius es pot facilitar reservant l'operació abans de portar-la a terme.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Dette projekt har en anderledes løsning på problemet. Det tilføjer understøttelse af virtuelle mapper i alle KIO-programmer, hvor linkene til filer og mapper midlertidigt kan gemmes for en session. Filerne og mapperne er "iscenesat" på den virtuelle mappe. Filer kan tilføjes til den ved at bruge alle de normale filhåndteringshandlinger såsom Flyt, Kopiér, Indsæt eller med træk-og-slip. Derfor kan komplekse filhandlinger, såsom at flytte filer på tværs af mange enheder gøres let, ved at iscenesætte handlingen inden den udføres.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Αυτό το έργο αποτελεί μια καινοτόμα λύση αε αυτό το πρόβλημα. Προσθέτει υποστήριξη εικονικών φακέλων σε όλες τις KIO εφαρμογές, όπου δεσμοί σε αρχεία και φακέλους αποθηκεύονται προσωρινά για μια συνεδρία. Τα αρχεία και οι φάκελοι «μπαίνουν στην άκρη» σε αυτόν τον εικονικό φάκελο. Αρχεία μπορούν να προστεθούν σε αυτόν με χρήση όλων των συνηθισμένων λειτουργιών διαχείρισης αρχείων όπως μετακίνηση, αντιγραφή και επικόλληση ή με έλξη και εναπόθεση. Άρα, σύνθετες λειτουργίες με αρχεία όπως η μεταφορά τους ανάμεσα σε πολλές συσκευές διευκολύνεται βάζοντας στην άκρη τη λειτουργία πριν αυτή να εκτελεστεί.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">This is project has a novel solution to this problem. This adds virtual folder support in all KIO applications, where the links to files and folders can be temporarily saved for a session. The files and folders are "staged" on this virtual folder. Files can be added to this by using all the regular file management operations such as Move, Copy and Paste, or by drag and drop. Hence, complex file operations such as moving files across many devices can be made easy by staging the operation before performing it.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Este proyecto proporciona una solución innovadora para este problema implementando carpetas virtuales a todas las aplicaciones que usan KIO, donde los enlaces a los archivos y carpetas se pueden guardar de forma temporal para una sesión. Los archivos y carpetas se «montan» en esta carpeta virtual. Puede añadir archivos usando las operaciones de gestión de archivos habituales, como mover, copiar y pegar, o arrastrar y soltar. Por consiguiente, puede realizar con facilidad operaciones de archivos complejas, como moverlos entre varios dispositivos, almacenando temporalmente la operación antes de realizarla.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tämä projekti on uusi ratkaisu ongelmaan. Se lisää kaikkiin KIO-sovelluksiin tuen virtuaalikansioille, jonne tiedostoja ja kansioita voi istunnon ajaksi väliaikaisesti tallentaa. Tässä virtuaalikansiossa tiedostot ja kansiot ovat ”välivaiheessa”. Niitä voi viedä sinne tavallisin tiedostonhallintatoimenpiten (siirto, kopiointi, liittäminen, veto ja pudotus). Monimutkaisia tiedostotoimintoja kuten tiedostojen siirtämistä laitteelta toiselle voi näin helpottaa luomalla toimintoon välivaiheen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Este proxecto fornece unha solución novedosa para este problema. Engade compatibilidade con cartafoles virtuais aos aplicativos que usen KIO, onde poder gardar as ligazóns a ficheiros e cartafoles de maneira temporal, gardados durante a sesión. Os ficheiros e cartafoles “resérvanse” neste cartafol virtual, ao que se lle poden engadir ficheiros usando as operacións habituáis de xestión de ficheiros como mover, copiar ou pegar, ou arrastrando e soltando. Deste modo, operacións complexas de ficheiros como mover ficheiros de moitos dispositivos poden simplificarse gardando as operacións na reserva antes de executalas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Projek ini memiliki solusi baru untuk masalah ini. Ini menambahkan dukungan folder virtual di semua aplikasi KIO, dimana tautan ke file dan folder dapat disimpan sementara untuk satu sesi. File dan folder "staged" pada folder virtual ini. File dapat ditambahkan ke sini dengan menggunakan semua operasi pengelola file biasa seperti Pindah, Salin, dan Tempel, atau dengan seret dan taruh. Oleh karena itu, operasi file yang kompleks seperti memindahkan file di banyak perangkat dapat dipermudah dengan mengatur operasi sebelum melakukannya.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">이 프로젝트는 이 문제를 해결하기 위한 방안을 제시합니다. 모든 KIO 프로그램에 가상 폴더 지원을 추가해서 현재 세션에서 사용할 수 있는 파일과 폴더의 임시 링크를 저장합니다. 파일과 폴더는 이 가상 폴더에 "임시로 저장"됩니다. 이동, 복사, 붙여넣기, 드래그 앤 드롭 등 일반적인 모든 파일 관리 작업으로 여기에 파일을 추가할 수 있습니다. 여러 장치로 파일을 이동하는 등의 복잡한 파일 작업은 실제 작업을 수행하기 전에 임시 폴더에 저장해서 쉽게 해결할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Dit project heeft een vernieuwende oplossing tot dit probleem. Dit voegt ondersteuning voor virtuele mappen toe aan alle KIO-toepassingen, waar de koppelingen naar bestanden en mappen tijdelijk in opgeslagen kunnen worden voor een sessie. De bestanden en mappen worden "staged" in deze virtuele map. Bestanden kunnen hieraan worden toegevoegd door alle reguliere bewerkingen bij bestandsbeheer zoals Verplaatsen, Kopiëren en Plakken of door slepen en loslaten. Complexe bestandsbewerkingen zoals verplaatsen van bestanden over vele apparaten kan gemakkelijk gemaakt worden door "staging" van de bewerking alvorens deze uit te voeren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Ten projekt ma nowe rozwiązanie na przedstawiony problem. Dodaje on obsługę wirutalnych katalogów we wszystkich aplikacjach KIO, w których odnośniki do plików i katalogów można tymczasowo zapisać dla sesji. Pliki i katalogi są "dobierane" do tego wirtualnego katalogu. Pliki można dodawać wykorzystując wszystkie zwyczajne działania na plikach takie jak przenieś, kopiuj, wklej lub przeciągnij. Dzięki temu, złożone działania na plikach takie jak przenoszenie plików z wielu urządzeń jest łatwiejsze poprzez przygotowanie działania przed jego wykonaniem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Este projecto tem uma solução nova para este problema. Adiciona o suporte para pastas virtuais em todas as aplicações do KIO, onde as ligações aos ficheiros e pastas podem ser gravadas temporariamente para uma dada sessão. Os ficheiros e pastas ficam "preparados" nesta pasta virtual. Poderá adicionar ficheiros à mesma se usar todas as operações normais de gestão de ficheiros, como o Mover, o Copiar e o Colar ou ainda por arrastamento. Deste modo, as operações complexas com ficheiros, como a mudança de posição dos ficheiros entre vários dispositivos pode ser feita facilmente se preparar a operação antes de a executar propriamente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Detta är ett projekt som har en originell lösning på problemet. Det lägger till stöd för virtuella kataloger i alla KIO-program, där länkar till filer och kataloger kan sparas tillfälligt under en session. Filerna och katalogerna "förbereds" i denna virtuella katalog. Filer kan läggas till i den genom att använda de vanliga filhanteringsåtgärderna såsom flytta, kopiera och klistra in, eller med drag och släpp. Därigenom kan komplexa åtgärder såsom att flytta filer mellan många enheter göras enkla genom att förbereda åtgärden innan den utförs.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Proje bu soruna yeni bir çözüm getiriyor. Bu, dosya ve klasörlere olan bağlantılar geçici olarak bir oturum için kaydedilebilen tüm KIO uygulamalarında sanal klasör desteği ekler. Dosyalar ve klasörler bu sanal klasörde "aşamalı" haldedirler. Dosyaları, Taşı, Kopyala ve Yapıştır gibi tüm normal dosya yönetimi işlemlerini kullanarak veya sürükleyip bırakarak ekleyebilirsiniz. Bu nedenle, birçok aygıt arasında dosya taşıma gibi karmaşık dosya işlemleri işlemi gerçekleştirmeden önce işlemi aşamalayarak kolaylaştırabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Цей проект пропонує новітнє вирішення проблеми. Програмними засобами створюється віртуальна тека в усіх програмах із підтримкою KIO. У цій теці протягом сеансу роботи можуть тимчасово зберігатися посилання на файли і теки. Ці файли і теки складають «стос» віртуальної теки. До стосу можна додавати нові запис за допомогою звичайних операцій із керування файлами — пересування, копіювання та вставлення — або за допомогою перетягування зі скиданням. Таким чином, складні дії з файлами, зокрема пересування файлів між багатьма пристроями можна доволі просто виконати, розмістивши файли у стосі до виконання копіювання.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThis is project has a novel solution to this problem. This adds virtual folder support in all KIO applications, where the links to files and folders can be temporarily saved for a session. The files and folders are "staged" on this virtual folder. Files can be added to this by using all the regular file management operations such as Move, Copy and Paste, or by drag and drop. Hence, complex file operations such as moving files across many devices can be made easy by staging the operation before performing it.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=filestash</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=filestash</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kio-stash/kio-stash.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
